# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Professional software development specialist with experience in web, cloud, mobile and desktop application development, and related areas. Quick to become familiar with the latest industry trends in web development technologies, while demonstrating a logical and analytical approach to detecting and solving complex problems using advanced tools and methods. Possesses excellent interpersonal and communication skills, and the ability to develop and maintain positive internal and external relationships. Enjoys being part of a successful team and thrives in high pressure and challenging work environments.

## Core Competencies/Areas of Expertise

Software Development • Web Content Management • Website Optimisation • Web Scripting Technologies • Data Management Information Technology • Troubleshooting • Web Banner Creation • Technical Support • Training • Customer Service

## **TECHNICAL EXPERTISE**

Packages: Git, Webpack, npm, Wordpress, Google Web Designer, Adobe Suite, Visual Studio Code, JetBrains Web Storm.

Technologies: Angular, React JS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3/SASS, Bootstrap, RESTful APIs, JSON, and GSAP.

# **SKILLS PROFILE**

## Information technology and software development

- Gained experience working in technical positions with various companies.
- Experienced in working on projects that have included web, cloud, mobile, desktop application development, in addition to developing test cases for each project.
- Has a solid theoretical understanding after completing a Diploma in Software Development (Level 7) from EDENZ Colleges in New Zealand, in addition to several certifications from reputable institutions.

## Teamwork, problem solving, and multitasking

- Works comfortably using own initiative, as well as in teams of varying size, duration, and complexity.
- Excellent collaborator and communicates well with team members at all levels to meet company objectives/ goals.
- Adept at investigating and analysing system incidents and applying corrective action, as well as providing various forms of technical support to clients.
- Demonstrates excellent problem-solving and trouble-shooting skills.
- Understands business requirement and delivers exceptional quality.

## Communication and customer service

- Interacts well with team members and clients alike to resolve technical issues.
- Trilingual ability enhances effective communication in a multicultural environment.
- Provides clear, professional, informative, and appropriate communication to colleagues and customers.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

First Security, Auckland, New Zealand

# Security Officer • 2020 – currently

- Identify any potential hazards or security risks and breaches.
- · Provide foot patrolling on site.
- Help people to stay safe during the lockdown.
- Gain knowledge of New Zealand workplace and team culture.

## Stanton Lab, Dnipropetrovsk, Ukraine

# Front-End Developer • 2015 – 2017

- Built responsive websites and landing pages from scratch using HTML/CSS, JavaScript, and an API to access data.
- Created web application using CMS such as Wordpress and Joomla.
- Developed creative web banners using Google Web Designer and GSAP.
- Created HTML email templates and newsletters for email marketing campaigns.

# **Key Achievements:**

Vlada Brusylo Resume

Executed and monitored standards for user interfaces, page design, and animation development.

## PRIVATBANK, Dnipropetrovsk, Ukraine

# Service Desk Analyst • 2012 – 2015

- Provided technical support to internal staff with the aim of resolving queries at the first point of contact.
- Diagnosed operational problems in the banking software.
- Transferred issues to the appropriate department to be resolved.
- Created tickets in the service desk system and analysed incoming incidents.

### **Key Achievements:**

- Honed problem solving, troubleshooting, and logical thinking abilities, as well as analytical skills.
- Developed the ability to work under pressure and quickly understand new business environments, issues, and data challenges

#### FREELANCE PROJECTS

http://vlada.rf.gd/

Website-resume: Created web pages using HTML, CSS Grid.

https://okflowers.org/

Website-portfolio: Created web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and then template was adapted for Wordpress.

https://granny-10517.web.app/

Food delivery service website: Created web pages using Angular, HTML, CSS/SCSS, TypeScript and Bootstrap.

https://portfolio-vlada.firebaseapp.com/

Floristic service landing page: Created web pages using HTML, CSS Flex/Grid, JavaScript.

# **EDUCATION AND PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT**

### EDENZ COLLEGES, New Zealand

# Diploma in Software Development (Level 7)

- Included units on Software Architecture; Software Architecture Quality Attributes (Reusability, Maintainability, IT Security, etc.);
   Software Requirements; Requirements UX, SDLC(agile, scrum, etc), and Testing.
- Created several projects, which included web and cloud application development (HTML, CSS Flex/Grid, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP, Heroku); mobile application development (Java, Android Studio); desktop application development (Java, XML); and an application development project (HTML, CSS, Materialize, Laravel, SQL, AWS). Also developed test cases for each project.

# DNIPROPETROVSK NATIONAL UNIVERSITY, Ukraine

## **Bachelor in Applied Science**

• Included units on ECM (Electronic Computing Machine) and Programming in Fortran, PL/1, Assembler; Methods of Computing and Computing Practicum; Optimisation Methods; Computer Science; and Mathematical Programming.

## COURSES/CERTIFICATIONS/LICENCES

Responsive Web Design Certification, freeCodeCamp

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification, freeCodeCamp

Quality Certificate of Advanced Training in C++, National Metallurgical Academy of Ukraine

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# Languages Spoken:

English, Russian, and Ukrainian.

#### Interests:

Aerial silks, amigurumi, and cooking.